Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Grafton, Henry FitzRoy, Duke of, 1790- 1863, 1852 (Box 28, Folder 1050)
  - Grafton, William Henry FitzRoy, Duke of, 1819-1882, 1879 (Box 28, Folder 1051)
  - Graham, James Robert George, Sir, Bart., 1792-1861, 1832-53, undated (Box 28, Folder 1052)
  - Graham, Thomas, 1805-1869, 1866, undated (Box 28, Folder 1053)
  - Grain, Corney, 1844-1895, 1875-89, undated (Box 28, Folder 1054)
  - Granby, C. W., 1856 (Box 28, Folder 1055)
  - Grant, Francis, Sir, 1803-1878, undated (Box 28, Folder 1056)
  - Grant, William Keir, Sir, 1772-1852, 1824 (Box 28, Folder 1057)
  - Grantham, William Wilson, 1866-1942, undated (Box 28, Folder 1058)
  - Granville, Charlotte (Stuart), undated (Box 28, Folder 1059)
  - Granville, Granville George Leveson- Gower, Earl, 1815-1891, 1851-87 (Box 28, Folder 1060)
  - Granville, Granville George Leveson- Gower, Earl of, 1872-1939, 1906 (Box 28, Folder 1061)
  - Graves, Alfred Perceval, 1846-1931, 1899 (Box 28, Folder 1062)
  - Graves, George, 1876-1949, undated (Box 28, Folder 1063)
  - Graves, Katy, undated (Box 28, Folder 1064)
  - Gray, Thomas, 1877 (Box 28, Folder 1065)
  - Great Britain. Lord Chamberlain., 1851-1909 (Box 29, Folder 1066)
  - Greene, Harry Plunket, 1865-1936, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 1067)
  - Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, 1845-68, undated (Box 29, Folder 1068)
  - Greet, Philip Ben, Sir, 1856-1936, undated (Box 29, Folder 1069)
  - Grego, Joseph, 1843-1908, 1904-05 (Box 29, Folder 1070)
  - Gregory, Mary Anne, Lady, 1815-1895
    See: Stirling, Fanny, 1815-1895, box 56, folder 2055
  - Gregory, Robert, 1819-1911, 1872-1901 (Box 29, Folder 1071)
  - Gregory, William, 1803-1858, undated (Box 29, Folder 1072)
  - Grenfell, Francis Wallace Grenfell, Baron, 1841-1925, undated (Box 29, Folder 1073)
  - Grenfell, H. R. (Henry Riverdale), 1824-1902, 1881 (Box 29, Folder 1074)
  - Grenfell, Lilian Maud (Spencer- Churchill), 1873-1951, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 1075)
  - Greville, Algernon William Fulke Greville, Baron, 1841-1909, undated (Box 29, Folder 1076)
  - Greville, Charles, 1794-1865, undated (Box 29, Folder 1077)
  - Grey, Charles, 1804-1870, 1856-70, undated (Box 29, Folder 1078)
  - Grey, George, Sir, 1799-1882, 1842-62, undated (Box 29, Folder 1079)
  - Grey, Henry George Grey, Earl, 1802- 1894, 1847-76 (Box 29, Folder 1080)
  - Grey, Sylvia, 1895 (Box 29, Folder 1081)
  - Grey of Fallodon, Edward Grey, Viscount, 1862-1933, 1893 (Box 29, Folder 1082)
  - Griffen, Robert, 1867 (Box 29, Folder 1083)
  - Griffiths, Arthur, 1838-1908, 1888 (Box 29, Folder 1084)
  - Grimthorpe, Edmund Beckett, Baron, 1816-1905, 1890-96 (Box 29, Folder 1085)
  - Grossmith, George, 1847-1912, undated (Box 29, Folder 1086)
  - Grossmith, Walter Weedon, 1853-1919, undated (Box 29, Folder 1087)
  - Grosvenor, Sibell Mary Lumley, Lady, 1855-1929 (later Wyndham), undated (Box 29, Folder 1088)
  - Grosvenor, Victor Alexander Grosvenor, Earl, 1853-1884, undated (Box 29, Folder 1089)
  - Grote, George, 1794-1871, undated (Box 29, Folder 1090)
  - Grove, George, Sir, 1820-1900, 1894 (Box 29, Folder 1091)
  - Grove, W. R. (William Robert), 1811- 1896, 1860-91 (Box 29, Folder 1092)
  - Guedalla, Philip, 1889-1944, 1924-26 (Box 29, Folder 1093)
  - Guest, Edwin, 1800-1880, 1868 (Box 29, Folder 1094)
  - Gull, William Withey, Sir, 1816-1890, 1870-72, undated (Box 29, Folder 1095)
  - Gully, Edward Walford Karslake Gully, 1870-1931, 1900-1901 (Box 29, Folder 1096)
  - Gully, Joseph Manby, 1808-1883, undated (Box 29, Folder 1097)
  - Gurdon, Eveline Camilla (Newton), Lady, 1858-1894, undated (Box 29, Folder 1098)
  - Gurney, John, Sir, 1768-1845, 1833 (Box 29, Folder 1099)
  - Gurney, Joseph, 1804-1879, 1836 (Box 29, Folder 1100)
  - Gurney, Samuel, 1786-1856, undated (Box 29, Folder 1101)
  - Guthrie, G. J. (George James), 1785- 1856, 1826, undated (Box 29, Folder 1102)
  - Gützlaff, Karl Friedrich August, 1803- 1851, undated (Box 29, Folder 1103)
  - Guyer, Maurice L., b. 1878, 1901 (Box 29, Folder 1104)
  - Gwydyr, Peter Robert Drummond-Burrell, Baron, 1782-1865
    See: Willoughby de Eresby, Peter Robert Drummond Burrel, Baron, 1782- 1865, box 63, folder 2316
  - Gye, Frederick, 1781-1869, 1829-69, undated (Box 29, Folder 1105)
  - Gye, Frederick, 1810-1878 (Box 29, Folder 1106)
  - Gye, Herbert A. F., 1879 (Box 29, Folder 1107)
  - Hackney, Mabel Lucy (Mrs. Laurence Irving), 1898 (Box 30, Folder 1108)
  - Haddington, Thomas Hamilton, Earl of, 1780-1858, 1842 (Box 30, Folder 1109)
  - Haddy, Frances, 1872 (Box 30, Folder 1110)
  - Haggard, Lilias Rider, 1892-1968, 1926, undated (Box 30, Folder 1111)
  - Halford, Henry, Sir, Bart., 1766-1844, 1844, undated (Box 30, Folder 1112)
  - Halifax, Charles Lindley Wood, Viscount, 1839-1934, 1865 (Box 30, Folder 1113)
  - Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800- 1885, 1840-80, undated (Box 30, Folder 1114)
  - Hall, Charles, Sir, 1814-1883, 1873 (Box 30, Folder 1115)
  - Hall, Edward Marshall, Sir, 1858-1927, 1915-26 (Box 30, Folder 1116)
  - Hall, S. C. (Samuel Carter), 1800-1889, 1844-79 (Box 30, Folder 1117)
  - Hallam, Henry, 1777-1859, undated (Box 30, Folder 1118)
  - Halsbury, Hardinge Stanley Giffard, Earl of, 1823-1921, 1883-1911, undated (Box 30, Folder 1119)
  - Hamilton, Anne, Lady, 1766-1846, undated (Box 30, Folder 1120)
  - Hamilton, Cicely Mary, 1872-1852, 1923, undated (Box 30, Folder 1121)
  - Hamilton, Claud, Lord, 1813-1884, undated (Box 30, Folder 1122)
  - Hamilton, Edward Walter, Sir, 1847- 1908, 1874-98 (Box 30, Folder 1123)
  - Hamilton, George Alexander, 1802-1871, undated (Box 30, Folder 1124)
  - Hamilton, George Francis, Lord, 1845- 1927, 1872-99, undated (Box 30, Folder 1125)
  - Hamilton, Godfrey, 1906-11 (Box 30, Folder 1126)
  - Hamilton, J., Capt., undated (Box 30, Folder 1127)
  - Hammersley, C., 1885 (Box 30, Folder 1128)
  - Hammond, Edmund Hammond, Baron, 1802- 1890, 1855-65 (Box 30, Folder 1129)
  - Hampden, Henry Bouverie William Brand, Viscount, 1814-1892, 1876-79, undated (Box 30, Folder 1130)
  - Hampton, John Somerset Pakington, Baron, 1799-1880, 1852-69, undated (Box 30, Folder 1131)
  - Hanbury, Lily, d. 1908, undated (Box 30, Folder 1132)
  - Hancock, William, 1835-36 (Box 30, Folder 1133)
  - Hanmer, Mrs., undated (Box 30, Folder 1134)
  - Hansell, Henry Peter, 1863-1935, 1908-12, undated (Box 30, Folder 1135)
  - Harcourt, William Vernon, Sir, 1827- 1904, 1877-1903, undated (Box 31, Folder 1136)
  - Harcourt-Smith, Cecil, Sir, 1859-1944, 1895 (Box 31, Folder 1137)
  - Hardalot, Guy d', 1858-1936
    See: Rhodes, Helen, 1858-1936, box 49, folder 1781
  - Hardwicke, Charles Philip Yorke, Earl of, 1799-1873, 1843-78, undated (Box 31, Folder 1138)
  - Hardwicke, Charles Philip Yorke, Earl of, 1836-1897, 1844 (Box 31, Folder 1139)
  - Hardwicke, Susan (Liddell) Yorke, Countess of, 1810-1886, 1862 (Box 31, Folder 1140)
  - Hare, John, 1844-1921, 1881-1913, undated (Box 31, Folder 1141)
  - Harewood, Henry Lascelles, Earl of, 1797-1857, 1836-48 (Box 31, Folder 1142)
  - Harley, John Pritt, 1786-1858, 1837-58, undated (Box 31, Folder 1143)
  - Harris, Augustus, Sir, 1852-1896, 1871-92, undated (Box 31, Folder 1144)
  - Harris, John, 1802-1856, 1847 (Box 31, Folder 1145)
  - Harrison, Clifford, 1897-98, undated (Box 31, Folder 1146)
  - Harrison, Frederick, d. 1926, 1895 (Box 31, Folder 1147)
  - Harrison, Frederick Ashall, b. 1860, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 1148)
  - Harrison, Mary St. Leger Kingsley, 1852-1931, 1892 (Box 31, Folder 1149)
  - Hart Dyke, William, Sir, 1837-1931, 1876, undated (Box 31, Folder 1150)
  - Hassard, John, 1871 (Box 31, Folder 1151)
  - Hastings, Flora Elizabeth Rawdon, Lady, 1806-1839, 1838 (Box 31, Folder 1152)
  - Hatherley, Charlotte (Moore) Wood, Baroness, 1804-1878, 1869, undated (Box 31, Folder 1153)
  - Hatherley, William Page Wood, Baron, 1801-1881, 1854-80 (Box 31, Folder 1154)
  - Havelock, Arthur Elibank, Sir, 1844- 1908, 1889-1900 (Box 31, Folder 1155)
  - Haweis, H. R. (Hugh Reginald), 1839- 1901, undated (Box 31, Folder 1156)
  - Hawkins, Edward, 1780-1867, 1850 (Box 31, Folder 1157)
  - Hawkins, Edward, 1789-1882, 1849-68, undated (Box 31, Folder 1158)
  - Hawkins, R. B. B., Mrs., undated (Box 31, Folder 1159)
  - Hawthorne, Grace, undated (Box 31, Folder 1160)
  - Hawtrey, Charles, 1858-1923, 1897-1902, undated (Box 31, Folder 1161)
  - Hayter, William Goodenough, Sir, 1792- 1878, 1853-57, undated (Box 31, Folder 1162)
  - Heathcote, G. J., undated (Box 32, Folder 1163)
  - Helena Augusta Victoria, Princess Christian of Schleswig-Holstein, 1846- 1923, 1866-1915, undated (Box 32, Folder 1164-1165)
  - Helena Friederike Auguste, Princess of Waldeck and Pyrmont, Duchess of Albany, 1861-1922, 1882-95 (Box 32, Folder 1166)
  - Helena Victoria, Princess of Great Britain, 1870-1948, 1943, undated (Box 32, Folder 1167)
  - Helps, Arthur, Sir, 1813-1875, 1857-74, undated (Box 32, Folder 1168)
  - Hemans, Felicia Dorothea Browne, 1793- 1835, 1881, undated (Box 32, Folder 1169)
  - Henley, Joseph Warner, 1793-1884, undated (Box 32, Folder 1170)
  - Henniker, John Henniker-Major, Baron, 1801-1870, 1832 (Box 32, Folder 1171)
  - Henry, Thomas, Sir, 1807-1876 (Box 32, Folder 1172)
  - Henry William Frederick Albert, Duke of Gloucester, 1900-1974
    See: Gloucester, Henry William Frederick Albert, Duke of, 1900-1974, Box 27, folder 1018.
  - Henschel, George, Sir, 1850-1934, 1900 (Box 32, Folder 1173)
  - Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, 1840-61, undated (Box 32, Folder 1174)
  - Herkomer, Hubert von, Sir, 1849-1914, 1884, undated (Box 32, Folder 1175)
  - Herschel, John F.W. (John Frederick William), Sir, 1792-1871, undated (Box 32, Folder 1176)
  - Hertfield, Thomas, undated (Box 32, Folder 1177)
  - Hertford, Francis Charles Seymour Conway, Marquis of, 1777-1842, 1825, undated (Box 32, Folder 1178)
  - Herschell, Farrer Herschell, Baron, 1837-1899, 1874-98, undated (Box 32, Folder 1179)
  - Hertford, Francis Hugh George Seymour, Marquess of, 1812-1884, 1877-83, undated (Box 32, Folder 1180)
  - Hertford, Richard Seymour-Conway, Marquess of, 1800-1870, 1842 (Box 32, Folder 1181)
  - Hertslet, Edward, Sir, 1824-1902, 1859 (Box 32, Folder 1182)
  - Hervey, Francis, Lord, 1846-1931, 1880 (Box 32, Folder 1183)
  - Hewett, Prescott, Sir, Bart., 1812- 1891, 1875-84, undated (Box 32, Folder 1184)
  - Hewitt, Agnes, 1894, undated (Box 32, Folder 1185)
  - Hicks, Seymour, Sir, 1871-1949, 1897-1928, undated (Box 32, Folder 1186)
  - Hicks, Ellaline (Terriss), 1872-1971
    See Terriss, Ellaline, 1872-1971, Box 58, folder 2116.
  - Hill, Matthew Davenport, 1792-1872, 1867 (Box 32, Folder 1187)
  - Hilton, Hilda, 1883 (Box 32, Folder 1188)
  - Hind, J. Russell (John Russell), 1823- 1895, 1881 (Box 32, Folder 1189)
  - Hippisley, G., 1819 (Box 32, Folder 1190)
  - Hobart, John Henry, 1775-1830, 1824 (Box 32, Folder 1191)
  - Hobart, Vere Henry Hobart, Lord, 1818- 1875, 1880, undated (Box 32, Folder 1192)
  - Hofmann, A. W., 1863 (Box 32, Folder 1193)
  - Hogg, James Weir, Sir, 1790-1876, undated (Box 32, Folder 1194)
  - Hole, S. Reynolds (Samuel Reynolds), 1819-1904, 1868-85, undated (Box 33, Folder 1195)
  - Holland, J. G. (Josiah Gilbert), 1819- 1881, undated (Box 33, Folder 1196)
  - Holless, William B., Sir, 1840 (Box 33, Folder 1197)
  - Hollingshead, Henry Randall, d. 1873, undated (Box 33, Folder 1198)
  - Hollingshead, John, 1827-1904, 1873-89, undated (Box 33, Folder 1199)
  - Holloway, W. J., 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1200)
  - Home, Charles Alexander Douglas-Home, Earl of, 1834-1918, 1886 (Box 33, Folder 1201)
  - Honey, George, 1822-1880, 1870, undated (Box 33, Folder 1202)
  - Hood, A. Nelson, 1893 (Box 33, Folder 1203)
  - Hood, Tom, 1835-1874, 1864, undated (Box 33, Folder 1204)
  - Hook, Theodore Edward, 1788-1841, 1820-39, undated (Box 33, Folder 1205)
  - Hook, Walter Farquhar, 1798-1875, 1838-72, undated (Box 33, Folder 1206)
  - Hooker, Joseph Dalton, Sir, 1817-1911, undated (Box 33, Folder 1207)
  - Hooker, William Jackson, Sir, 1785- 1865, 1842 (Box 33, Folder 1208)
  - Horner, Louise, undated (Box 33, Folder 1209)
  - Horsley, Fanny
    See: Whitelaw, Fanny (Horsley), Lady, box 63, folder 2291
  - Horsley, J. W. (John William), 1845- 1921, 1886 (Box 33, Folder 1210)
  - Horsman, Edward, 1807-1876, 1864-74, undated (Box 33, Folder 1211)
  - Horton, Miss P., 1838 (Box 33, Folder 1212)
  - Hothfield, Henry James Tufton, Baron, 1844-1926, 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1213)
  - Hotten, John Camden, 1832-1873, 1861 (Box 33, Folder 1214)
  - Houghton, Richard Monckton Milnes, Baron, 1809-1885, 1838, undated (Box 33, Folder 1215)
  - Howard, George James, Earl of Carlisle, 1843-1911, 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1216)
  - Howard, Henry, Sir, 1843-1921, undated (Box 33, Folder 1217)
  - Howard of Penrith, Esme William Howard, Baron, 1863-1939, 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1218)
  - Howard de Walden, Frederick George Ellis, Baron, 1830-1899, undated (Box 33, Folder 1219)
  - Howe, Georgiana Elizabeth (Spencer- Churchill) Curzon-Howe, Countess, 1860-1960, 1883, undated (Box 33, Folder 1220)
  - Howley, William, 1766-1848, 1825-47, undated (Box 33, Folder 1221)
  - Howson, Charles E., 1898 (Box 33, Folder 1222)
  - Hudson, George, 1800-1874, 1864 (Box 33, Folder 1223)
  - Hudson, George Bickersteth, 1845-1912, undated (Box 33, Folder 1224)
  - Hughes, Annie, 1869-1931, 1889-1903 (Box 33, Folder 1225)
  - Hugon, Anne, 1880 (Box 33, Folder 1226)
  - Hume, Fergus, 1859-1932, undated (Box 33, Folder 1227)
  - Hume, Joseph, 1777-1855, 1840, undated (Box 33, Folder 1228)
  - Hunt, Frederick Knight, 1814-1854, 1859 (Box 33, Folder 1229)
  - Hunt, George Ward, 1825-1877, 1874-75, undated (Box 33, Folder 1230)
  - Hunt, William Holman, 1827-1910, 1875 (Box 33, Folder 1231)
  - Huntly, Charles Gordon, Marquess of, 1847-1937, 1880 (Box 33, Folder 1232)
  - Hutchinson, George Andrew, 1841-1913, 1896 (Box 33, Folder 1233)
  - Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895, undated (Box 33, Folder 1234)
  - Hylton, William George Hylton Jolliffe, Sir, Baron, 1800-1876, undated (Box 33, Folder 1235)
  - Iddesleigh, Lady Cecilia Frances (Farrer) Northcote, Duchess of, 1823- 1910, undated (Box 34, Folder 1236)
  - Iddesleigh, Stafford Henry Northcote, Earl of, 1818-1887, 1865-89 (Box 34, Folder 1237)
  - Iddesleigh, Walter Stafford Northcote, Earl of, 1845-1927, 1875-1923 (Box 34, Folder 1238)
  - Ince, William, 1825-1910, 1898, undated (Box 34, Folder 1239)
  - Inge, William Ralph, 1860-1954, undated (Box 34, Folder 1240)
  - Ingelow, Jean, 1820-1897, 1884 (Box 34, Folder 1241)
  - Inglefield, E. A. (Edward Augustus), 1820-1894, 1871 (Box 34, Folder 1242)
  - Inglis, Robert Harry, Sir, 1786-1865, 1814-56, undated (Box 34, Folder 1243)
  - International Horticultural Exhibition, 1865-66 (Box 34, Folder 1244)
  - Irving, Ethel, undated (Box 34, Folder 1245)
  - Irving, Henry, Sir, 1838-1905, 1881-1905, undated (Box 34, Folder 1246)
  - Irving, H. B. (Henry Broadribb), 1870- 1919, 1898-1907, undated (Box 34, Folder 1247)
  - Irving, Isabel, 1871-1944, undated (Box 34, Folder 1248)
  - Jackson, Blomfield, 1839-1906, undated (Box 35, Folder 1249)
  - Jackson, John, 1811-1885, 1835-84, undated (Box 35, Folder 1250)
  - James, C. J., 1857 (Box 35, Folder 1251)
  - James, David, 1839-1893, 1883-89 (Box 35, Folder 1252)
  - James, Edwin John, 1812-1882, 1860, undated (Box 35, Folder 1253)
  - James, G. P. R. (George Payne Rainsford), 1801?-1860, 1823 (Box 35, Folder 1254)
  - James of Hereford, Henry James, Baron, 1828-1911, 1869-1905, undated (Box 35, Folder 1255)
  - Janviers, Dr., undated (Box 35, Folder 1256)
  - Jay, Isabel, 1901, undated (Box 35, Folder 1257)
  - Jecks, Clara, b. 1865?, 1891-1908, undated (Box 35, Folder 1258)
  - Jekyll, Joseph, 1754-1837, 1815 (Box 35, Folder 1259)
  - Jenner, William, Sir, 1815-1898, 1877-88, undated (Box 35, Folder 1260)
  - Jerome, Jerome K. (Jerome Klapka), 1859-1927, 1890-1926 (Box 35, Folder 1261)
  - Jerrold, Douglas William, 1803-1857, undated (Box 35, Folder 1262)
  - Jerrold, Blanchard, 1826-1884, 1868-69 (Box 35, Folder 1263)
  - Jersey, George Child-Villiers, Earl of, 1773-1859, undated (Box 35, Folder 1264)
  - Jersey, Sarah Sophia (Fane) Child, Countess of, 1785-1867, 1847, undated (Box 35, Folder 1265)
  - Jesse, Edward, 1780-1868, 1845-61 (Box 35, Folder 1266)
  - Jessel, George, Sir, 1824-1833, 1878-82 (Box 35, Folder 1267)
  - Jessopp, John, 1863 (Box 35, Folder 1268)
  - John, Augustus, 1878-1961, undated (Box 35, Folder 1269)
  - Johnson, James Johnson William Prior, d. 1845 (Box 35, Folder 1270)
  - Johnson, John, Lord Mayor of London, 1846 (Box 35, Folder 1271)
  - Jones, Henry Arthur, 1851-1929, 1894-97 (Box 35, Folder 1272)
  - Jones, Richard, 1779-1851, 1849 (Box 35, Folder 1273)
  - Jopling, Louise, 1843-1933, undated (Box 35, Folder 1274)
  - Josephs, Fanny, 1881 (Box 35, Folder 1275)
  - Josephs, Patty, undated (Box 35, Folder 1276)
  - Jourdain, Henry John, Sir, 1835-1901 (Box 35, Folder 1277)
  - Jowett, Benjamin, 1817-1893, 1870-91, undated (Box 35, Folder 1278)
  - Keeley, Mary Ann (Goward), 1805?-1899, 1849-98, undated (Box 36, Folder 1279)
  - Keeley, Robert, 1793-1869, undated (Box 36, Folder 1280)
  - Kelland, Philip, 1808-1879, 1860 (Box 36, Folder 1281)
  - Kelly, Fitzroy, Baron, 1796-1880, 1831-75 (Box 36, Folder 1282)
  - Kemble, Charles, 1775-1854, undated (Box 36, Folder 1283)
  - Kemble, Fanny, 1809-1893, undated (Box 36, Folder 1284)
  - Kendal, Madge, 1849-1935, 1879, undated (Box 36, Folder 1285)
  - Kendal, William Hunter, 1843-1917, 1901 (Box 36, Folder 1286)
  - Kennedy, C.M. (Charles Malcolm), 1831- 1908, 1881 (Box 36, Folder 1287)
  - Kenmare, Valentine Augustus Browne, Earl of, 1825-1905, 1880, undated (Box 36, Folder 1288)
  - Keon, Miles Gerald, 1821-1875, 1845-46, undated (Box 36, Folder 1289)
  - Keppel, Derek, Sir, 1863-1944, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 1290)
  - Keppel, Henry, Sir, 1809-1904, undated (Box 36, Folder 1291)
  - Kerr, Lucy, Hon., 1871 (Box 36, Folder 1292)
  - Kimberly, John Wodehouse, Earl, 1826- 1902, 1855-96, undated (Box 36, Folder 1293)
  - King, P. J. Locke (Peter John Locke), 1811-1885, 1873, undated (Box 36, Folder 1294)
  - Kingscote, Robert Nigel Fitzhardinge, Sir, 1830-1908, 1869, undated (Box 36, Folder 1295)
  - Kingsdown, Thomas Pemberton-Leigh, Baron, 1793-1867, 1841-63, undated (Box 36, Folder 1296)
  - Kingsley, Charles, 1819-1875, 1859, undated (Box 36, Folder 1297)
  - Kingston, Gertrude, d. 1937, 1910, undated (Box 36, Folder 1298)
  - Kiralfy, Imre, 1845-1919, 1899, undated (Box 36, Folder 1299)
  - Knight, Charles, 1791-1873, undated (Box 36, Folder 1300)
  - Knightley, Rainald Knightley, Baron, 1819-1895, 1881-85, undated (Box 36, Folder 1301)
  - Knollys, Elizabeth Charlotte, Hon., d. 1930, 1908, undated (Box 36, Folder 1302)
  - Knollys, Francis Knollys, Viscount, 1837-1924, 1863-1912 (Box 36, Folder 1303)
  - Knollys, William Thomas, Sir, 1797- 1883, 1865-87, undated (Box 36, Folder 1304)
  - Knowles, James Thomas, Sir, 1831-1908, 1890-91 (Box 36, Folder 1305)
  - Labouchere, Henry Du Pré, 1831-1912, 1857-98, undated (Box 37, Folder 1306)
  - Lacy, Thomas Hailes, 1809-1873, 1871 (Box 37, Folder 1307)
  - Lacy, Walter, 1809-1898, 1878 (Box 37, Folder 1308)
  - Laking, Francis Henry, Sir, 1847-1914, 1901-10, undated (Box 37, Folder 1309)
  - Landseer, Charles, 1799-1879, undated (Box 37, Folder 1310)
  - Landseer, Edwin Henry, Sir, 1803-1873, 1851-69, undated (Box 37, Folder 1311-1312)
  - Lane, Grace, 1902, undated (Box 37, Folder 1313)
  - Lane, Richard James, 1800-1872, undated (Box 37, Folder 1314)
  - Langdale, Henry Bickersteth, Baron, 1783-1851, 1843-45, undated (Box 37, Folder 1315)
  - Langtry, Jeanne, b. 1862, undated (Box 37, Folder 1316)
  - Langtry, Lily, 1852-1929, undated (Box 37, Folder 1317)
  - Lankester, Phepe (Pope), d. 1900, 1862, undated (Box 37, Folder 1318)
  - Landsdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863, 1805-50, undated (Box 37, Folder 1319)
  - Landsdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805, 1783 (Box 37, Folder 1320)
  - Lathom, Edward Bootle-Wilbraham, Earl, 1837-1898, 1886 (Box 37, Folder 1321)
  - Law, Arthur, 1844-1913, 1902 (Box 37, Folder 1322)
  - Law, Hugh, 1818-1883, 1887 (Box 37, Folder 1323)
  - Lawrence, John Laird Mair Lawrence, Baron, 1811-1879, 1860-77, undated (Box 37, Folder 1324)
  - Layard, Austin Henry, Sir, 1817-1894, 1856-83, undated (Box 37, Folder 1325)
  - Leach, John, 1760-1834, 1827-30 (Box 38, Folder 1326)
  - Leclercq, Carlotta, 1840?-1893, 1867 (Box 38, Folder 1327)
  - Leclercq, Rose, 1845?-1899, undated (Box 38, Folder 1328)
  - Lee, Frederick George, 1832-1902, 1884 (Box 38, Folder 1329)
  - Lee, Nelson, 1806-1872, 1850, undated (Box 38, Folder 1330)
  - Lee, R., Mrs., 1791-1856, 1837 (Box 38, Folder 1331)
  - Lee, Vernon, 1856-1935, 1883-85 (Box 38, Folder 1332)
  - Leeds, Francis Godolphin D'Arcy- Osborne, Duke of, 1798-1859, undated (Box 38, Folder 1333)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard, 1866-1947, undated (Box 38, Folder 1334)
  - Leighton, Edwin Blair, 1853-1922, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 1335)
  - Leighton of Stretton, Frederic Leighton, Baron, 1830-1896, 1894, undated (Box 38, Folder 1336)
  - Leiningen, Edward Leopold Victor, Prince, 1830-1904, 1883-87 (Box 38, Folder 1337)
  - Leitch, William Leighton, 1804-1883, 1878 (Box 38, Folder 1338)
  - Lemon, Mark, 1809-1870, undated (Box 38, Folder 1339)
  - Lennox, Adelaide, undated (Box 38, Folder 1340)
  - Lennox, John George, Lord, 1793-1873, 1841 (Box 38, Folder 1341)
  - Lennox, William Pitt, Lord, 1799-1881, 1872 (Box 38, Folder 1342)
  - Leno, Dan, 1860-1904, undated (Box 38, Folder 1343)
  - Leo, Rosa, 1886 (Box 38, Folder 1344)
  - Leopold George Duncan Albert, Duke of Albany, 1853-1884, 1881-83, undated (Box 38, Folder 1345)
  - Le Queux, William, 1864-1927, undated (Box 38, Folder 1346)
  - Leslie, Frederick, 1855-1892, 1886-93 (Box 38, Folder 1347)
  - Leslie, John, SIr, 1766-1832, undated (Box 38, Folder 1348)
  - Lestocq, W., 1880 (Box 38, Folder 1349)
  - Leveson-Gower, Albert, Lord, 1843-1874, undated (Box 38, Folder 1350)
  - Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806- 1863, 1838-59, undated (Box 38, Folder 1351)
  - Liddell, Henry George, 1811-1898, undated (Box 38, Folder 1352)
  - Liddell, Thomas Atherton Powys, Baron, 1801-1861, 1837-43 (Box 38, Folder 1353)
  - Lincolnshire, Charles Robert Wynn Carington, Marquess, 1843-1928, 1874 (Box 38, Folder 1354)
  - Lind, Letty, b. 1862, undated (Box 38, Folder 1355)
  - Lindley, Nathaniel Lindley, Baron, 1828-1921, 1887-95 (Box 38, Folder 1356)
  - Linnell, John, 1792-1882, 1871 (Box 38, Folder 1357)
  - Lister, Reginald, Sir, 1865-1912, 1888, undated (Box 38, Folder 1358)
  - Liverpool, Charles Cecil Cope Jenkinson, Earl of, 1784-1851, 1841-47 (Box 38, Folder 1359)
  - Lloyd, Marie, 1870-1922, 1894, undated (Box 38, Folder 1360)
  - Lochlin, R., 1870-72 (Box 39, Folder 1361)
  - Lockhart, J. G. (John Gibson), 1794- 1854, 1843 (Box 39, Folder 1362)
  - Lockwood, Frank, Sir, 1846-1897, 1894, undated (Box 39, Folder 1363)
  - Lockyer, Joseph Norman, Sir, 1836-1920, undated (Box 39, Folder 1364)
  - Loftus, Kitty, undated (Box 39, Folder 1365)
  - Londesborough, Albert Denison, Baron, 1805-1860, 1832-60, undated (Box 39, Folder 1366)
  - Londesborough, William Henry Forester Denison, Earl of, 1834-1900, 1896, undated (Box 39, Folder 1367)
  - London Royal College of Surgeons of England, 1886 (Box 39, Folder 1368)
  - Londonderry, Charles William Vane, Marquess of, 1778-1854, 1833-49, undated (Box 39, Folder 1369)
  - Longley, Charles Thomas, 1794-1868, 1844-67, undated (Box 39, Folder 1370)
  - Lonnen, Edwin Jesse, d. 1901, 1896 (Box 39, Folder 1371)
  - Lopes, Lopes Massey, Sir, Bart., 1818- 1908, 1844-90 (Box 39, Folder 1372)
  - Louis, Prince, Grand Duke of Hesse, 1837-1892, 1868 (Box 39, Folder 1373)